<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Balsamroot Consulting</title>
    <link>/saulgill/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Balsamroot Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/saulgill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Feasibility study for Nez Perce Tribe</title>
      <link>/saulgill/blog/2017/12/17/winery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/blog/2017/12/17/winery/</guid>
      <description>Completed a feasibility study for a winery for the Nez Pearc Tribe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community needs assessment for family health clinic</title>
      <link>/saulgill/blog/2017/09/17/needs-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/blog/2017/09/17/needs-assessment/</guid>
      <description>Community Needs assessment for the community council of idaho&amp;rsquo;s community family health clinic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of after school program</title>
      <link>/saulgill/blog/2017/06/01/evaluation-after-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/blog/2017/06/01/evaluation-after-school/</guid>
      <description>We completed a evaluation of 21st century learning community after school program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposal for health clinic building</title>
      <link>/saulgill/blog/2016/09/17/proposal-clinic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/blog/2016/09/17/proposal-clinic/</guid>
      <description>Wrote a proposal for the building for Community Family Health Clinic for the Commmunity Council of Idaho and was funded for $300,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strategic plan</title>
      <link>/saulgill/blog/2015/11/11/another-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/blog/2015/11/11/another-project/</guid>
      <description>Wrote a strategic plan for the Community Council of Idaho, the largest nonprofit in the state of idaho serviceing latinX communites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessment and Planning</title>
      <link>/saulgill/services/planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/services/planning/</guid>
      <description>Our team can help you assess the needs of your service population and plan and evaluate health, education, and community interventions. We can determine the local and regional economic impacts of an activity to evaluate its outcomes or understand its feasibility.
 Needs assessments, gap analyses, feasibility studies, and strategic plans Community and public health assessments and planning Economic assessments and modeling  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/saulgill/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/contact/</guid>
      <description> Ready to start a conversation? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darin Saul, PhD</title>
      <link>/saulgill/team/darin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/team/darin/</guid>
      <description>Darin has dedicated his 23-year career to addressing the needs of people, communities, and the environment. Darin has a doctorate in English and has written over 160 successful proposals to foundations, corporations, and government funders. Darin&amp;rsquo;s experience includes owning and directing Ecovista, an environmental research and planning company that specialized in watershed assessment and planning. He also co-founded and was later the executive director of the Groundworks Institute, a nonprofit that provided environmental education programs and coordinated stream and wetland restoration projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grant Writing and Organizational Development</title>
      <link>/saulgill/services/grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/services/grant/</guid>
      <description>We work on all parts of the funding puzzle, including funder research, campaign planning, and proposal writing. We can help with strategic planning and support documents - anything you need to strengthen your organization and be competitive.
 Foundation, government, and corporate funders Funding plans and grant-based campaigns Strategic plans, annual reports, outreach and marketing materials Project and program evaluation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research and Data Collection</title>
      <link>/saulgill/services/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/services/data/</guid>
      <description>We collect data in English and Spanish with surveys, interviews, and focus groups, and we analyze data using quantitative and qualitative approaches.
 Web-based indicator tracking, including health indicators Feasibility studies and business plans Qualitative (narrative) and quantitative data analysis Data management Indicator identification, prioritization, and performance measure development  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soren Newman, PhD</title>
      <link>/saulgill/team/soren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/team/soren/</guid>
      <description>A social scientist by training, Soren collects meaningful data that empowers organizations to affect change. Soren is skilled in interview, focus group, and survey methodologies as well as participatory research. She also has experience in grant development, project evaluation, and strategic planning. Soren was raised in a rural community in northcentral Idaho where her passion for and commitment to the diverse peoples and landscapes of the Northwest grew. Her interest in understanding how conservation, economic, and social objectives can simultaneously be achieved motivated her to earn a doctoral degree in Natural Resource and Environmental Science from Washington State University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing and Editing</title>
      <link>/saulgill/services/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/saulgill/services/writing/</guid>
      <description>We can help you research, write, and produce a wide variety of documents, including proposals, reports, plans, marketing materials, curriculum, and communications.
 Writing and editing of all types in English and Spanish Presentation of data Coaching and training Social marketing  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>